{
    "subject": "resource/Sinopharm",
    "predicate": "ontology/locationCountry",
    "object": "resource/China",
    "human_readable": "Sinopharm is located in China.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9770892262458801,
            "question": "Is Sinopharm based in China?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8536313772201538,
            "question": "Is Sinopharm a Chinese company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8535298109054565,
            "question": "Where is Sinopharm located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7360036969184875,
            "question": "What country is Sinopharm in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6096230745315552,
            "question": "To which country does Sinopharm belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5811352133750916,
            "question": "Where would you find Sinopharm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5048686265945435,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Sinopharm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3927082419395447,
            "question": "What is the origin of Sinopharm?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1257622241973877,
            "question": "Can you name a company located in China?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10882651060819626,
            "question": "Which company is known for being in China?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sinopharm is located in China.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6045_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a company located in China?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6045_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin of Sinopharm?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6045_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Sinopharm?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6045_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6045_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6045_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6045_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6045_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6045_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6045_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6045_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6045_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6045_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6045_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the context information contains multiple documents, including one (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6045/re-ranker-msmarco/14.txt) where it explicitly states that Sinopharm Group is \"China's leading distributor and retailer of pharmaceuticals, healthcare products, and medical devices\", confirming its location in China."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which indicate that companies like Sinopharm are based or operate in China."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}